# Chandrasekhar Varma Jagadabi

Ongole, Andhra Pradesh, India



chandu.jagadabi@gmail.com

**(**+91) 9398432203



linkedin.com/in/chandrasekhar-varma-jagadabib4571717a

#### Overview

I am an ambitious, energetic college student working towards non-profit organization management industry. My contributions to FEPSI (Forum for Empowering People through Social Innovation and entertainment) proves my leadership abilities. FEPSI is a student-based NGO in VIT.

As a Director of Event Management, I have worked on varied position including Skills in Python (Programming Language), Microsoft Word, CSS3, Front Page, and HTML5. Strong operations professional with a B Tech -Bachelor of Technology focused in Computer Science from Vellore Institute of Technology.

### **Experience**



#### ϔ Digital Marketing Associate

**NinthSem** 

Oct 2020 - Present (3 months +)

#### Responsibilities:

- Build, plan and implement over all digital marketing strategics.
- Stay up to date with latest technology with best practices.
- Manage and over see different marketing channels.
- Providing different strategies on how to promote the organization in social medias.
- Strategies to promote through advertisement for enhanced reach.
- Joined as Campus Ambassodor and promoted in span of 2 months.

# Web developer

#### **AGIXURY**

Oct 2020 - Present (3 months +)

#### Responsibilities:

- Front-end team lead.
- Create Website template/User Interface
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs.
- Assigning everyday tasks on front-end part
- Working out with GitHub if any glitches workout on those.

#### DIRECTOR OF EVENTS

F.E.P.S.I

Mar 2020 - Present (10 months +)

#### Responsibilities:

- Assist the project leads in creation of event description, flow and other technicalities.
- Event management for Gravitas and Riviera.

- Handling permission and logistics for expo.
- Responsible for checking the budgets for the events.
- Maintenance of attendance of each event conducted.
- Gathering pre and post event requirements.

#### **Education**



#### Vellore Institute of Technology

BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science (Pursuing) 2018 - 2022



# 🧙 Sri Chaitanya College of Education

Intermediate 2016 - 2018



#### K.T.R HIGH SCHOOL

10th standard 2015 - 2016

#### **Skills**

- Front-end Development
- C (Programming Language)
- JAVA
- Python (Programming Language)
- HTML5
- Data Structures

- **Public Relations**
- Social Media
- GitHub
- **Bootstrap**
- Microsoft Word
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

#### **Honors & Awards**



## VITEEE Merit Scholarship Holder - Vellore Institute of Technology

Oct 2018

I am receiving 48,500/- every year for getting 965th rank in VITEEE.